that too
Mm because maybe Robin Han hasn't either
very indented the perception of time
just disappear i just felt that i
wanted that Rose as soon as possible
lied both in front of me and and Daniel Och
that's what made us both
started to fizz up eh Do you think that Sand
lies about what he says Eh so it is
it's hard to say what gram has
you and we will ride Mountain bikes min
sense of Valentin is very good Han
feels very warm harmonious and happy
bubbly but also very loving
and get my hopes up on this one
started something eh Sandra but they have said
as you say l as I said stir the pot
TR also thinks it treats here now against
me and call me a liar It's not
nice too I haven't called